<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MAD Class Project</string>

    <string name="html">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Admissions</h1>
        <p>To be unconditionally admitted to complete UCC undergraduate programmes,
        individuals should possess a minimum of <b>five (5) subjects at the GCE or CSEC level </b>
        (including the mandatory English Language and Mathematics) at grades A, B, C or 1, 2, 3
        respectively. A CSEC pass at level 3 must have been obtained since 1998.
        </p>
        <p>Candidates who have a minimum of <b>4 CXCs</b> can also apply pending the outstanding
        CXC subjects or can opt to do UCC replacement courses Core Mathematics, English for Academic
        Purpose and Fundamentals of Accounting.
        </p>
        <p>Candidates can opt to apply under the Mature Entry option. To be accepted, applicants
        must be working for <b>5 years</b> or more and be at a minimum age of <b>25 years</b>.
        Academic qualifications, a detailed resume, a job letter and 3 professional references
        will be required.
        </p>
      <style>
      a.button {
        display: inline-block;
        background-color: #7b38d8;
        border-radius: 10px;
        border: 4px double #cccccc;
        color: #eeeeee;
        text-align: center;
        font-size: 20px;
        padding: 18px;
        width: 250px;
        -webkit-transition: all 0.5s;
        -moz-transition: all 0.5s;
        -o-transition: all 0.5s;
        transition: all 0.5s;
        cursor: pointer;
        margin: 5px;
      }
    </style>
    <a href="https://ucc.edu.jm/apply/undergraduate/preform" class="button">Tap Here to Apply</a>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="staff_dir">
        <item>Adrian-Leigh Gilman \n
            Adjunct Lecturer \n
            Email: agilman@ucc.edu.jm\n
            Phone: 876-555-1234
        </item>
        <item>Lori-Ann Gordon \n
            IT Lecturer \n
            Email: lgordon@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-4321
        </item>
        <item>Miguel Gill\n
            IT Lecturer \n
            Email: mgill@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-5544
        </item>
        <item>Kerry Berry\n
            Programme Coordinator \n
            Email: kberry@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-5566
        </item>
        <item>Lisa Smith\n
            IT Lecturer \n
            Email: lsmith@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-7766
        </item>
        <item>Natalie Rose\n
            IT HOD \n
            Email: nrose@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-8894
        </item>
        <item>Otis Osbourne\n
            IT Lecturer \n
            Email: oosbourne@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-8894
        </item>
        <item>Henry Osborne\n
            IT Lecturer \n
            Email: hosbourne@ucc.edu.jm \n
            Phone: 876-555-8894
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_list">
        <item>ITT105 Computer Troubleshooting and Repairs. This introductory course in computer
            troubleshooting and repairs is designed to give students hands-on experience in diagnosing
            and solving some of the common hardware and software problems that can occur during the
            normal usage of a computer. </item>
        <item>ITT201 Data Communications and Networks I
            This introductory course in Data Communications and Networks is designed to give students an
            understanding of networks and how they can be used in organizations to increase efficiency.
            It will also introduce IP addressing and subnets and briefly look at security issues in networking.</item>
        <item>ITT102 Discrete Mathematics I
            This course will introduce students to the basic idea as to how computer systems are designed and provide
            a realistic picture of the internal workings and design of computer systems.</item>
        <item>ITT200 Object-Oriented Programming using C++ This course aims to broaden the student’s knowledge of concepts
            and features of an object-oriented programming language. Students will be required to use these concepts to
            design solutions for real world problems.</item>
        <item>ITT203 Data Structures and File Management I
            This is an introductory course in data structures and file management. It will introduce the concepts
            of data structures and file management so that students become more familiar with how data is organized
            and manipulated. It provides students with the theoretical framework for further advanced practical
            studies in data structures and file management.</item>
        <item>ITT301 Data Structures and File Management II
            This is an advanced practical course in data structures and file management. It will broaden the knowledge gained
            in Data Structures and File Management I. The course introduces the student to additional data structures
            such as trees, sets, graphs, and advanced techniques in sorting (internal and external).</item>
        <item>ITT405 Human Computer Interaction and Interface Design
            This course examines the interaction between humans and computers and explores the design of computer
            interfaces that are based on the abilities, limitations, and goals of the users. Students will be introduced
            to the principles underlying the interaction of humans with computers and the design of computer interfaces
            by reviewing the theories and current research in the area.</item>


    </string-array>


</resources>